wholesomeyum.com 2016-10-21

# Privacy | Wholesome Yum - Natural, gluten-free, low carb recipes. 10 ingredients or less.

**General Statement About Privacy**  
Wholesome Yum is committed to maintaining the privacy and protection of your personal information when you visit this website. This policy outlines what information may be collected when you visit the site, and how that information is used. When you continue to visit this website, you are consenting to the practices described in this policy.

**Information Collected When Leaving Comments**  
When you leave comments on Wholesome Yum, you have the option of providing your name, blog or website url, or other information. This information becomes a permanent part of the website when you provide it with a comment, and can be seen by other visitors to the site.

**Information Collected Through Tracking Software**  
All websites which collect traffic data have the ability to monitor visitor information such as IP addresses, browser type, operating system, location, date/time of visit, and information about which areas of the site are visited. At Wholesome Yum, we monitor such information, but do not store it in permanent files or attempt to link it to individual site visitors.

**Information Collected by Third Party Advertisers**  
Wholesome Yum uses third party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the website. These companies may use information (NOT including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies (see below). We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. We may use advertising service vendors to help present advertisements on the website, one of which is [http://www.gourmetads.com](http://www.gourmetads.com/). These vendors may use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In doing so, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by these advertising service vendors is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours, and Service Provider disclaims all liability in connection therewith.

**Information Collected by Google AdSense**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website. The [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher’s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user’s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this sites and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**How We Use Cookies**  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**Advertiser Privacy Policies**  
If you would like to contact the Advertisers to learn more about their privacy policies and what options (if any) they offer to opt out of their data collection and use, please follow these links to their Web sites:

Lijit Networks Inc.  
<http://www.gourmetads.com/about/privacy-policy>

BlogHer Publishing Network  
<http://www.blogher.com/privacy-policy>

Lijit Networks Inc.  
<http://www.lijit.com/company/privacy-policy>

Some of these third party advertising networks are participants in the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”), a cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies committed to building consumer awareness and establishing responsible business and data management practices and standards. You can learn more about NAI and how you may “opt out” of targeted advertising delivered by NAI member ad networks [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. 

**Contacting  Wholesome Yum Regarding This Policy**  
If you have any questions about this policy please contact wholesomeyum (at) gmail (dot) com

**Changes to This Policy**  
We reserve the right to update or change this privacy policy at any time. Any such change, modification, or addition to the privacy policy on Wholesome Yum will become effective immediately upon posting on the site.

This policy was last updated on March 28, 2016.
